JordanCostley.com

Jordan Costley

User Experience Designer

the Jordan Costley@gmail.com linked in.com/in/Jordan Costley

I believe in the process of iterative, human-centered design to create intuitive, meaningful solutions with a focus on user goals while maintaining business goals. I create responsive digital experiences based on data and research.

Education

BS Interactive Design | Kennesaw State University

Minor in Technical Communication

Projects

PlanIt Prototype | Research, Interaction, UI/UX

- Collaborated with three team members to produce a mobile student planner app prototype utilizing human-centered UX design methods.
- Designed wireframes, created UI elements, and established interactions for the high-fidelity prototype based on user research.
- Conducted usability testing to refine the design to produce a finalized prototype.

Spotter Prototype | Team Lead, Research, Interaction, UI/UX

- Led two team members to produce a mobile streaming assistant app prototype.
- Conducted user research interviews to establish user goals and behaviors.
- Oversaw and collaborated on the design process of creating wireframes, user flows, UI elements, interaction design, and for the high-fidelity prototype.

Experience

Photographer | Freelance

August 2018 - Present

- Collaborate with local and national brands to create product photography for web content and advertising material.
- Photograph portraits and headshots in addition to events including engagement sessions and wedding ceremonies.

Sales Associate | FedEx Office

July 2016 - March 2019

- Worked alongside a small team to advise guests with their shipping needs.
- Collaborated with customers to evaluate their printing needs and produced solutions including the design of any pre-press requirements.
- Counted, verified, and reconciled daily cash sales.
- Trained and mentored new team members for the Atlanta district.

Skills

Technical

- Wireframes
- Mockups
- User flows
- Rapid Prototyping
- Task Analysis
- Cognitive Walk-through
- User Research
- Usability Testing
- Information Architecture
- User Interface Design
- Heuristic Evaluation
- Interaction Design
- HTML, CSS, & Javascript

Tools

- Figma
- InVision
- Axure
- Adobe XD
- Illustrator
- InDesign
- Photoshop

Recognition

- Dean's List 2016-2020
- President's List:
 Fall 2018, 2019
 Spring 2020